twelve initiatory steps in becoming a
man one built true Brotherhood with
other men to detach from and create a
grown-up relationship with your mother
three master your sexual energy for the
fundamental meditation experience I am
NOT my thoughts emotions and bodily
sensations five master aggression and
fear prove discipline and commitment six
embrace and integrate your inner
feminine seven honor your father but
become your own man eight accept death
as a fact of life and as a path of
evolution 9 find and live your souls
mission living from a place of meaning
10 deal with and thrive amongst highly
feminine women without losing your focus
and without being an asshole 11 changed
your perspective radically once in a
while and 12 and 12 embrace mysticism
embrace the unknown
you